A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - J-M, 1977-1981; 17
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - A-Z (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - M - Miscellaneous (Box 299, Folder 1-2)
  - Medicine, 1977-1981; 18
    - Medicine - A-American C (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Medicine - American D-C (Box 300, Folder 1-4)
    - Medicine - C-L (Box 301, Folder 1-5)
    - Medicine - M-O (Box 302, Folder 1-4)
    - Medicine - P-T (Box 303, Folder 1-4)
    - Medicine - U-Z (Box 304, Folder 1-3)
    - Alcoholism (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholism - National Council on Alcoholism (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Alcoholism - National Council on Alcoholism New York City Affiliate, Inc. (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholism - LSR (Box 305, Folder 2-3)
    - American Cancer Society (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - American Cancer Society - New York City Division (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - American Cancer Society - New York City Division - LSR (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Arthritis Foundation and Chapters (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Medicine - Health Policy Advisory Center (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Hospice Inc. (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - New York Blood Center (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - New York Blood Center - Finances (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - New York Blood Center - Minutes-Meetings (Box 307, Folder 3, Box 308, Folder 1)
    - New York Blood Center - Printed Matter (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Pasteur Institute - Paris, France (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Society for the Right to Die, Inc. (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - A-H (Box 309, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - I-O (Box 310, Folder 1-5)
    - Hospitals - P-Z (Box 311, Folder 1-3)
    - Hospitals - The Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center Fund, Inc. (Box 311, Folder 5, Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Eisenhower Medical Center (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - A-B (Box 312, Folder 3-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - C-D (Box 313, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - E-L (Box 314, Folder 1-5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - L-T (Box 315, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - U-Z (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 316, Folder 2-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Reports, 1972-1981 (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Managers (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Overseers (Box 317, Folder 4-5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Trustees (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board-Committees (Structures and Responsibilities) (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Clippings (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Directory of Officers and Board Members (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances (Box 319, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open in 2029.
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Audits (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances-Budget (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Contributions, Bequests, Grants in cash (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Bequests-Pooled Income Trust (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Financial Data Chart Book (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Investment Data (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Audit Committee (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Committee on Financial Policy (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Pension Performance Review Committee (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Status of Capital Program (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Summary Financial Information (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - General (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Annual Appeal (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - A (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - B-G (Box 324, Folder 1-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - H-M (Box 325, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - M-S (Box 326, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - S-Z (Box 327, Folder 1-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Lee Coombe Memorial Library (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Norman and Rosita Winston Foundation (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - A-C (Box 328, Folder 2-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - C-I (Box 329, Folder 1-5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - J-R (Box 330, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - S-Z (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development - Insurance Industry (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development - Luncheons (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development - Chairman's and President's Luncheon, 1979 December 10 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development - Chairman's and President's Luncheon, 1978 March 10 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development-Securities Industry Campaign (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development - Xerox Luncheon, 1979 June 27 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - Minutes-Meetings (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Corporate Development Committee - Reports (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Japan, 1978-1980 (Box 333, Folder 2-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Luncheons (Box 334, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Frank Sinatra Benefit, 1979 October 28 (Box 334, Folder 3, Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Frank Sinatra Benefit II, 1981 (Box 335, Folder 2-4, Box 336, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fund Raising - Frank Sinatra Fund (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Interferon Program (Box 337, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Confidential
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Interferon - Mathilde Krim (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Legal (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Annual Meetings (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Managers (Box 338, Folder 2-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Overseers (Box 339, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board on Scientific Policy (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Trustees (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Joint Nominating Committee and Nominating Committee (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Joint Organizational Policy Committee and Organizational Policy Committee (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Members of the Corporation (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Miscellaneous Committees (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Presidency Search, 1979-1980 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Material (Box 341, Folder 4, Box 342, Folder 1-3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter - Center News (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Reports (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Arnold and Marie Schwartz International Hall of Science for Cancer Research Dedication (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Releases (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Works of Art (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Managers (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases - Minutes-Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Staff (Box 344, Folder 1-4, Box 345, Box 346, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Personnel
    - Hospitals - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases - Finances (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Finances (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan Kettering Institute for Cancer Research (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Minutes-Meetings (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Managers (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Trustees (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Minutes-Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - MSKCC - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Minutes-Meetings - Members of the Corporation (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Hospitals - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Minutes-Meetings (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, Tarrytown, NY (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Printed Matter (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Prospect Hospital Medical Foundation (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - Minutes-Meetings (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - A-Z (Box 349, Folder 3-4)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Board of Overseers (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Contributions (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Finances (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Hospitals - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Overseers (Box 349, Folder 8, Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - The Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund of New York (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund of New York - Printed Matter (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health - A-Z (Box 351, Folder 1-2)
    - Mental Health - Chase, Karen (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - Mental Health - Massachusetts Association for Mental Health, Inc. (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health - Printed Material (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Narcotics - A-Z (Box 352, Folder 3-4)
    - Narcotics - American Council on Marijuana and other Psychoactive Drugs (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Narcotics - Phoenix House and Foundation (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Printed Matter (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Printed Matter - Cancer (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Government (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - NIH - Printed Matter - Reports (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH - National Cancer Institute (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH - National Cancer Institute Advisory Board (Box 354, Folder 3-4)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH - National Cancer Institute - Printed Matter-Reports (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH - National Cancer Institute Advisory Board - Minutes-Meetings (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Government - HEW - Public Health Services - NIH - National Cancer Institute Advisory Board - Printed Material (Box 355, Folder 3-4)
  - N-P, 1977-1981; 19
    - N - Miscellaneous (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - O - Miscellaneous (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - P - Miscellaneous (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Philanthropy - A-C (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Philanthropy - C-N (Box 357, Folder 1-4)
    - Philanthropy - O-Z (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Philanthropy - Coalition of National Voluntary Organizations (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Philanthropy - New York Community Trust (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Philanthropy - Printed Matter (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Philanthropy - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Book (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Puerto Rican Affairs (Box 380, Folder 6)
  - Politics, 1977-1981; 20
    - Politics - A (Box 359, Folder 3-5)
    - Politics - B-Co (Box 360, Folder 1-4)
    - Politics - Co-H (Box 361, Folder 1-4)
    - Politics - H-M (Box 362, Folder 1-5)
    - Politics - N-Rep (Box 363, Folder 1-4)
    - Politics - Req-Z (Box 364, Folder 1-3)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - A-B (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - C-L (Box 365, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - M-R (Box 366, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - R-Z (Box 367, Folder 1-2)
    - Assassination Information Bureau (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Democracy Project (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Common Cause (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Fair Campaign Practices Committee (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Minority Legislation Education Program (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - New Directions (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - New Directions - David Rockefeller (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - New York Republican State Committee (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - Republican National Finance Committee (Box 370, Folder 1-2)
    - Republican National Finance Committee - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Republican Senatorial Committee (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Republican Senate-House Dinner, 1979 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - Ripon Society (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - Westchester Republican County Committee (Box 371, Folder 3)
    - Printed Material - (re. Shah) (Box 371, Folder 4)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV (Jay) - West Virginia (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV (Jay) - West Virginia - Inauguration, 1977 (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV (Jay) - West Virginia - Inauguration, 1981 (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV (Jay) - Printed Material (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - New York State - A-G (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - New York State - H-Z (Box 373, Folder 1-4)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - New York State - Attica Prison (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - A-Z (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - Supportive Activities - A-Z (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - Vice Presidency - A-Z (Box 374, Folder 3)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - Vice Presidency - Campaign '76, 1976 (Box 374, Folder 4)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - Vice Presidency - Farewells - A-M (Box 374, Folder 5)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - United States Government - Vice Presidency - Farewells - N-Z (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - Population, 1977-1981; 21
    - Population - A-Z (Box 375, Folder 2-3)
    - Abortion - A-M (Box 375, Folder 4)
    - Abortion - N-Z (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - The Alan Guttmacher Institute (Box 376, Folder 2-3)
    - Maternity Center Association (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Printed Material (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Draper World Population Fund (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Contributions (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Contributions (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - The Alan Guttmacher Institute - Contributions (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - Abortion - National Abortion Rights Action League (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - Population Council (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - Population Council - Contributions (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - Population Council - Board of Trustees (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - Population Council - Finances (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Population Council - Minutes-Meetings (Box 378, Folder 5, Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Population Council - Printed Material (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Population Education Inc. - General Correspondence (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - Population Education Inc. - Annual Reports (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - Population Education Inc. - Film Production (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Population Education Inc. - By-Laws (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - Population Education Inc. - Contract Modern Talking Pictures (Box 379, Folder 7)
    - Population Education Inc.- Grants Film - PEI (Box 379, Folder 8)
    - Population Education Inc. - HEW (Box 379, Folder 9)
    - Population Education Inc. - Project on Human Sexual Development (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Population Education Inc. - Tax Status (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Population Education Inc. - Relationship to PHSO (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Population Education Inc. - Report to Founders (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - House of Representatives - Select Committee on Population (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Q-R, 1977-1981; 22
    - Q - Miscellaneous (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - Race Relations - A-O (Box 381, Folder 2-5)
    - Race Relations - P-Z (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Race Relations - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law' (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - Race Relations - Institute for Southern Studies (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Race Relations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - Race Relations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Contributions - Legal Defense Education Fund, Inc. (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Race Relations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Contributions - Special Contributions Fund (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - Race Relations - National Conference of Black Lawyers (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - Race Relations, 1977-1981 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - Race Relations - National Urban League - Printed Material (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate, 1977-1981; 23
    - Real Estate (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Real Estate - A-M (Box 384, Folder 3-5)
    - Real Estate - N-Z (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Embarcadero Center, 1976-1977 (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - Embarcadero Center - Opening (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - Embarcadero Center - Finances (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - Embarcadero Center - General Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - Embarcadero Center - Block 232 (Box 386, Folder 3-5, Box 387, Folder 1)
    - Embarcadero Center - Block 232 and Block 233 (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - Embarcadero Center - Partnership Restructure (Box 387, Folder 3, Box 388, Folder 1-5)
    - Embarcadero Center - J. Richardson Dilworth (Box 389, Folder 1)
    - Embarcadero Center - Four (Box 389, Folder 2-4, Box 390, Folder 1-2)
    - Estate Fountain River - A-I (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Estate Fountain River - J-Z (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Estate Fountain River - Finances (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - Estate Fountain River - Park (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - Estate Fountain River - Sale - A-M (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - Estate Fountain River - Sale - N-Z (Box 392, Folder 1)